hertzcarsales.com 2016-04-13

# Car Sales Privacy Policy

                        Car Sales Privacy Policy
YOUR PRIVACY: We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal data we
hold about you. This policy explains what data we collect about you, how we collect it, the measures we
take to keep your data secure and the uses and disclosures we make of it. We also explain the options
you have regarding your personal data. When you request services from us, access our websites, utilize
our mobile “apps” or otherwise interact with us, for example, but without limitation, through our kiosks, our
in-vehicle technology, our official corporate pages on third party social networks (such as Facebook) or
the “apps” on those pages, you consent to our collection, retention and use of your personal data in the
manner described in this policy and accept the risks outlined in the Security section. You can quickly
review the key topics by reading the following overview or you may continue to scroll down to read more
about an issue or to read the full policy.
                                                 Overview
Scope                                                  Collection
Who We Are: We are The Hertz Corporation               What We Collect: We collect the personal
and its subsidiaries. This policy does not cover our   data we need to provide the services you request
licensees or affiliates or other third parties through from us, for our operational uses and disclosures
whom you may interact with us. This policy does not    (see below) or for such other purposes as you
cover our Dollar Rent A Car, our Thrifty Rent A Car    authorize.
or our Firefly Rent A Car businesses, or our Donlen    Sources: We mostly collect your data directly
Corporation subsidiary.
                                                       from you, through various channels, and
Legal Issues: We aim to comply with the privacy from companies involved in our provision of
laws applicable to the personal data we collect and    services to you, including our licensees.
use.                                                   Websites: Certain technologies are used on our
Changes: We may change this policy from time to websites, our apps and other ecommerce media,
time. The policy was last updated on 29 May 2014. including cookies and Pixel Tags, to collect data
                                                       about your visit to our site and sites upon which we
                                                       advertise. You may choose to restrict the use of
                                                       cookies as suggested in this policy but we do not
                                                       respond to a web browser’s “do not track” signals,
                                                       or mechanisms similar to such signals.
Retention                                              Uses and Disclosures
Storage: We generally retain personal data about Operational Uses: By providing your personal
our customers for as long as we believe appropriate data to us, you consent to our use and disclosure
for the purposes for which it was collected.           of your data for the operational purposes listed in
Security: We aim to maintain appropriate               this policy.
physical, procedural and electronic safeguards to      Marketing Uses: We would like to use your
protect your personal data.                            personal data for our marketing purposes. We may
Access and Correction: You may access and also want to share your data with our business
                                                       partners for their marketing purposes. You can
review the personal data we retain about you and
                                                       choose to restrict or “opt out” of these uses by
correct any factual errors.
                                                       following the instructions in this policy.

CONTACT US: We hope this policy answers your questions about our collection, use and
disclosure of your personal data. If it does not, or if you have any questions, please contact us by
following the instructions in the Contact Us section below.

                                                         Privacy Policy
YOUR PRIVACY
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal data we hold about you. This policy
explains what data we collect about you, how we collect it, the measures we take in our efforts to keep
your data secure and the uses and disclosures we make of it. We also explain the options you have in
relation to your personal data.
When you request services from us, operate a vehicle with in-vehicle technology, access our websites,
utilize our mobile “apps” or otherwise interact with us, for example, but without limitation, through our
kiosks, our official corporate pages on third party social networks (such as Facebook) or the “apps” on
those pages, you consent to our collection, retention and use of your personal data in the manner
described in this policy and accept the risks outlined in the Security section.
SCOPE
This policy covers the personal data we collect about you in connection with our car sales business which
identifies you as an individual. This policy does not cover the personal data we collect about you in
connection with our other businesses, including our car or equipment rental businesses, except for rentals
associated with your potential vehicle purchase. Any rentals associated with your purchase or potential
purchase of a vehicle is governed by this Privacy Policy and our privacy policy for our rental businesses.
This policy does not address data that does not personally identify you as an individual, for example, but
without limitation, aggregated anonymous data, IP addresses, computer operating systems, personal
preferences, vehicle identification numbers, etc. We are free to use data that does not identify you as an
individual as we wish. This policy does not apply to data collected by third party social networks (such as
Facebook), mobile device manufacturers, third party “mobile apps”, wireless service providers, internet
service providers or the operators of any networks through which you may interact with us and we
expressly disclaim any responsibility for the data collection, privacy or data security practices of those
entities. With regard to pages on third party social networks, this policy only applies to personal data we
collect through our pages (those with a direct link to this policy) and does not apply to any “unofficial”
pages or pages of our affiliates or licensees. Our websites are not directed to individuals under the age
of 13, and we do not knowingly obtain personal data from such individuals.
Who We Are
--------------------------------------------------------
We are The Hertz Corporation, a U.S. company, which, together with our subsidiary companies, provides
and supports vehicle rental and vehicle sales services worldwide. All references in this policy to “we”, “us”
and “our” are to us and our subsidiaries. Our businesses generally operate under a “Hertz” mark,
including Hertz Car Sales, Hertz Rent2Buy, Hertz Rent A Car, Hertz Local Edition, Hertz Claims
Management, and Hertz Equipment Rental Corporation. However, neither our Dollar Rent A Car or
Thrifty Rent A Car businesses operated by Dollar Thrifty Automotive Group, Inc., a Hertz subsidiary, our
Firefly Rent A Car business, nor our Donlen Corporation subsidiary, to the extent they may be engaged in
car sales, are covered by this policy because each of those entities/operations has its own privacy policy.
We also operate equipment rental businesses and, to a lesser extent, equipment sales, and claims
administration businesses; which are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
We operate a network of licensees in provision of our services worldwide and are affiliated to many other
companies through ownership. As our licensees and affiliates are independent companies, they are not
owned or controlled by us and are not covered by this policy, although they may have their own privacy
policies to govern the personal data they collect. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of our
licensees and affiliates.
More about subsidiaries, licensees and affiliates…

Subsidiaries: These companies are owned by The Hertz Corporation and are covered by this policy to the extent they may be engaged in
the car sales business. The expressions “we”, “us” and “our” apply to them, except for Dollar Thrifty Automotive Group, Inc. which operates
the Dollar Rent A Car and Thrifty Rent A Car businesses, Firefly Rent A Car, LLC, and Donlen Corporation which operates a fleet leasing
and fleet management business.
Licensees: We have a network of independent companies licensed to operate vehicle rental and vehicle sales businesses using the “Hertz”
name and business system. These companies may describe themselves as “Hertz System Licensees” or “Hertz Franchisees” to indicate
that they are not our subsidiaries.
Affiliates: These companies either control us (through ownership) or are controlled by the companies that control us. They cover a range of
businesses but are generally not involved in provision of our services to you.
Legal Issues
--------------------------------------------------------
We do business in many countries and aim to comply with the privacy laws applicable to the personal
data we collect and use.
The Hertz Corporation and those of its subsidiaries operating within the United States of America, comply
with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by
the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, retention and use of personal information
from European Union member countries and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe
Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and
enforcement. You can visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/ to learn more about the U.S.-E.U. and
U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor programs.
Changes
--------------------------------------------------------
We may change this policy from time to time. If we do so, the amended policy will take effect when we
post it on the applicable website(s), mobile “apps” or our third party social network page(s). Whenever we
make a change, we will amend the “last updated” notice under the “Scope” heading in the “Overview”
section above.
If any change makes the policy less protective of your personal data, such change will not apply to data
we collected about you before the change was made. The only exception to this is, unless legally
prohibited, where we have provided you with notice about the changes and given you the opportunity to
tell us not to apply them to your personal data.
COLLECTION
We collect a range of data about you from a variety of sources for the purposes of our business. The
examples we provide here are illustrative rather than a complete list of our practices.
What We Collect
--------------------------------------------------------
We collect the personal data and the non-personal data we need to provide the services you request from
us and for our operational uses in connection with such services, which may include:
      ·     Name, address and contact details, including telephone and mobile number, and email address;
      ·     Date and place of birth, social security number, passport number and driver’s license number and,
            upon our request, a copy of your driver’s license;
      ·     Your gender and photo;
      ·     Employer(s) name, address, and phone number, along with your employment and salary history;
      ·     Information to verify your identity;
      ·     Duration and ownership of your vehicle(s) and residence(s), your vehicle preferences and your
            other assets and liabilities;

      ·     Credit card and banking information;
      ·     Affiliations with or sponsorships by companies, associations, colleges or cities;
      ·     Location data such as geographic location of electronic devices used to contact us or to access
            our mobile “apps” or of the vehicle you have rented;
      ·     Information regarding the vehicle and its operation during your rental, if any;
      ·     Information regarding your transactions with us, our affiliates and others, such as the
            identification number of any vehicle you purchase from us and the method by which you finance
            any vehicle purchase;
      ·     Rental charges you incur and other information relating to your transactions with us;
      ·     Information transmitted by your computer’s browser software; and
      ·     Information about your credit history or other publicly available information about you from
            consumer reporting agencies.
We may collect certain personal data that constitutes sensitive data in some countries, such as data
about health conditions or membership of a trade union. Depending upon applicable local law, we may
be unable to process such sensitive data without your consent.
More about sensitive data…
Data about your health conditions is regarded as sensitive in many countries. If you ask us to accommodate a disability, such as by
provision of hand controls, or if there is an accident and we need to work with insurance and claims management companies relating to any
injury you may incur, we may need to process data about your health conditions. Similarly, in the EU, at least, your membership of a trade
union or similar organization is regarded as sensitive and we may need to process this information if you use a CDP Number that only
members of that union or organization can use.
Please note that if you wish to buy a vehicle from or rent with us or our licensees and need to provide sensitive data, you consent
to that data being collected, used, retained and disclosed for our Operational Uses. We will not use sensitive data about you for
marketing purposes.
Sources
--------------------------------------------------------
We collect personal data directly from you in connection with a reservation (even an abandoned or
interrupted reservation), a rental of a vehicle in connection with the purchase of a vehicle from us, when
you contact us to purchase a vehicle, when you purchase a vehicle from us, or when you register an
account with Hertz Car Sales, including information you provide:
      ·     When you call our reservation, customer contact or member care centers;
      ·     On our websites;
      ·     Through our kiosks;
      ·     On our mobile “apps”;
      ·     On our official third party social network pages;
      ·     Through your computer’s web browser;
      ·     At rental locations;
      ·     At our car sales locations;
      ·     Through our in-vehicle technology or through other telematic devices;
      ·     When you complete a vehicle purchase agreement and related documents, or apply for financing
            through us for financing the purchase of a vehicle; and
      ·     When you register an account with Hertz Car Sales.
We also gather personal data about you from a variety of other sources, which may include:
      ·     Transactions you complete with us and our licensees, including options you take, charges you
            incur and any incidents or accidents that may occur;

       ·    Sponsors of any Discount Code (as described below) you use in connection with the purchase of
            a vehicle from us;
       ·    To the extent you have made such information available, from third party social networks;
       ·    Consumer reporting agencies; and
       ·    Other companies that have business relationships with us, such as our licensees, affiliates and
            business partners, including airlines, hotels, financial service providers, and insurance companies.
Websites
--------------------------------------------------------
Our Websites
Certain technologies are used on our websites and on mobile devices to collect data about your visit or
usage, as follows:
      Cookies
A “cookie” is a set of data sent to your computer or mobile device by a web server that enables the
server to recognize your computer or mobile device.
Cookies help improve the quality of your visits to websites, for example, but not limitation, by making the
reservation process faster and smoother. The information the cookies provide helps in the development
of content and features that may be of interest to you.
We use cookies to:
       ·    Track your use of our websites during a single visit, remember the data you provide and the
            choices you make as you progress from page to page (“session cookies”); and
       ·    Recognize you at your next visit (“persistent cookies”).
Third party cookies may also be used on our websites for the purpose of:
       ·    Such third parties providing goods or services to you (for example, but without limitation, an
            insurance carrier paying or reimbursing you for a vehicle in connection with insurance
            replacement rentals);
       ·    Performing services on our behalf;
       ·    Facilitating business transactions with or through such third parties; or
       ·    Providing advertisements to you.
More about cookies…
By adjusting your browser or installing certain software, you can restrict our use of cookies. If you do this, you should be aware of the
following:
• If you restrict our use of session cookies you will not be able to use our websites or certain features of our e-mail messages. You should
be aware that session cookies are generally deleted or made unavailable to us as soon as you close your browser.

• If you restrict our use of persistent cookies you may still enjoy the full workings of our websites and e-mail messages but will need to re-
enter some data when starting a new website session. Although persistent cookies will neither automatically be erased nor made unavailable
to us upon closing your browser, they will typically “expire” after a number of years.
If you are still unsure about cookies, please note that our cookies are unable to retrieve other data from your computer’s hard drive or pass
on computer viruses.
      Pixel Tags
In addition, “pixel tags”, “web beacons”, “JavaScript”, or similar technologies that enable, among other
things, the tracking of your actions as a user of various websites or recipient of e-mail messages. (“Pixel
Tags”) may be used. Pixel Tags may be used in connection with our web pages, our online advertising, or
our e-mail messages, either by Hertz or by our service providers, business partners or other third parties.
Pixel Tags are used to collect typically anonymous data to help identify types of information, including
popular destinations, average rental prices, quote and conversion rates, click-throughs and other
information to improve the service you receive or the relevance of advertising directed to you. Pixel Tags
may also be used to identify which online advertisement or email has brought you to a website.
Further, certain Pixel Tags may be used by other companies for the purpose of tracking visits to their
websites, identifying if such internet traffic came from a Hertz website or confirming your eligibility to
receive services or benefits from such other companies.
Third party cookies or Pixel Tags may collect information about a user of our site’s online activities over
time and across different web sites.
Some of our web sites may use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and other, similar technologies (e.g.
Pixel Tags) to collect information about website use anonymously and reports trends, without identifying
individual visitors. To learn more about Google Analytics, including how to opt out of it, visit
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements regarding goods and services that
may be of interest to you when you access and use our websites and other websites, based on
information relating to your access to and use of our websites and other websites. To do so, these
companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of Pixel
Tags). If you would like to learn more about this practice, including your choices with respect to it, please
visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/.
We do not respond to a web browser’s “do not track” signal, or other mechanism that indicates a request
to disable online tracking of individuals who use or visit our websites.
As the internet and other eCommerce channels continue to develop, we may deploy and utilize different
types of technologies to collect data regarding your visit or usage.
      Blogs or Message Boards
Some of our websites and our official corporate pages on third party social networks (such as Facebook)
may provide functionality that permits you to post public messages or responses to articles, comments or
other postings. You should be aware that by submitting such a posting, including any personal data or
non-personal data in connection with it, you intend for that posting and any data in connection with it to be,
and it shall immediately become, public and as such will not be subject to this Privacy Policy. We reserve
the right to remove any posting or content in a posting at our sole discretion.
Other Company Websites

Our websites and e-mail messages may contain links to websites operated by other companies. You
should be aware that the collection, retention and use of any data you provide on these websites will be
governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the website and not by this policy.
RETENTION
We try to ensure that the personal data we retain about you is stored securely and, in light of the
information provided to us, is as accurate, current, ,complete and relevant as necessary for the purposes
for which we use and disclose it.
Storage
--------------------------------------------------------
We generally retain personal data about our customers for as long as we believe appropriate for the
purposes for which it was collected or as otherwise required or authorized by applicable law.
Our principal databases for storing the personal data we collect are located in New Jersey and Oklahoma,
U.S.A.
Security
--------------------------------------------------------
As you may be aware, there is no completely secure method of transmitting or storing data. Although their
physical characteristics are different, postal mail, telephone calls, text messages, faxes and transmissions
over the Internet or wireless networks all present possibilities of loss, misrouting, interception and misuse
of the data that is transmitted.
We take commercially reasonable measures to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access
or disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal data by aiming to maintain appropriate physical,
procedural and electronic safeguards to protect your personal data, including:
      ·     Restricting access to personal data to our employees or service providers on a “need to know”
            basis;
      ·     Enforcing policies and procedures for our employees in their handling of personal data; and
      ·     Using technologies designed to safeguard data during its transmission, such as SSL
            encryption for the data you provide on our websites.
If you have reason to believe that any account with us is no longer secure, you must immediately contact
us by following the instructions at the end of this policy.
More about SSL encryption…
“SSL” stands for Secure Sockets Layer encryption. We use this protection when you submit personal data to us on our websites. SSL
encryption seeks to ensure that you are actually sending your data to us and that no-one else can read or tamper with it during transmission.
When you are asked to provide your personal data to us on our website, you will see that our “http” website address changes to read "https".
The additional “s” denotes that the site is secure for that data transfer. You may also see a closed padlock symbol on your screen, again
denoting a secure site.
Security of Communications
We try to strike a balance between the security of your data and your convenience. As a result, we may
sometimes use a method of communication that is less secure than a less convenient alternative.
For example, but not limitation, we will send you an e-mail or a text message in unencrypted form (i.e.
instantly readable) because many of our customers are unable to access encrypted (i.e. coded) e-mail or
messages. This means that our message, if misrouted or intercepted, could be read more easily than

encrypted messages. For this reason, please do not include confidential information, such as your credit
card or drivers’ license number, in any e-mail or text you send to us or on any posting you make to a
public area of a third party social network page, especially since any such posting immediately becomes
public.
For a more secure way to communicate with us over the Internet, please click on the “Contact Us ” link
on any page of www.hertzcarsales.com, or www.hertz.com, and follow our instructions.
Access and Correction
--------------------------------------------------------
You may access and review your personal data, change it and correct factual errors as follows:
      ·     If you are a member of one of our membership programs, such as Hertz Gold Plus Rewards, or
            similar program, you may update your member profile by logging into the Hertz Gold Plus
            Rewards section of www.hertz.com.
      ·     If you have a created an account with Hertz Car Sales, you may update your Hertz Car Sales
            Account profile in the “My Account” link found on any page of www.hertzcarsales.com.
      ·     If you are not a member of one of our membership programs or registered with Hertz Car Sales,
            or your interest is broader than your membership data, or you wish us to correct or delete certain
            of your personal data, please contact us by following the instructions at the end of this policy.
To protect your privacy and the security of your personal data, we will take steps to verify your identity
before granting you access or making corrections to the data we store about you.
Certain types of personal data may need to be updated with the third party social network through which
you may interact with us, rather than directly with us.
USES and DISCLOSURES
Your personal data will not be used in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it was
collected or as authorized by you. In that regard, by enrolling in one of our membership programs,
creating an account with Hertz Car Sales, making a reservation with us, or buying a vehicle from us, you
consent to our use and disclosure of your personal data for the operational uses listed below which may
include disclosure of your data outside your country of residence. We would also like to use and disclose
your data for marketing purposes.
Operational Uses and Disclosures
--------------------------------------------------------
The examples provided below are illustrative and not a complete list of our practices:
To provide you services
We will share your personal data among ourselves, our agents, our licensees, other companies and
governmental agencies to provide services to you, including to:
      ·     Make your rental reservations and obtain a vehicle for a test rental or traditional test drive;
      ·     Process and/or confirm your vehicle purchase transaction(s) and provide related services,
            including the sale of ancillary products (such as vehicle protection plans) and the processing of
            your vehicle title and registration;

      ·     Assist you with obtaining financing for your vehicle purchase, including the processing of
            financing documentation/application materials
      ·     Provide you with customer assistance, including , but not limited to, assistance after you have
            initiated but not completed a reservation;
      ·     Provide you with complementary or trial services in connection with the vehicle purchase (such as
            satellite radio providers or in-vehicle remote services);
      ·     Bill and collect amounts owed, arising from, or in connection with your transactions with us ; and
      ·     For customer satisfaction and market research purposes to help us improve our services.
To communicate with you
We may use your personal data to communicate with you regarding:
      ·     Any of your transactions with us, including any rental reservation you initiate in connection with
            the potential purchase of a vehicle from us;
      ·     Your membership/status in one of our membership programs or your account with Hertz Car
            Sales; or
      ·     Changes to the terms or features of any of our membership programs to which you belong or any
            account you may have with Hertz Car Sales.
So that we may communicate with you, you give us your consent to call you on or send text messages to
your mobile telephone/device. You also consent to our use of auto-dialers and pre-recorded messages in
connection with any such telephone call or text message, including calls or texts to mobile telephone
numbers. We will not charge you for such calls or texts. Your mobile service provider will charge you
according to the applicable plan to which you subscribe.
Disclosure to companies you use
We will also share your information with companies you use in connection with your transaction,
including:
      ·     Your credit card provider and other companies that process your charges;
      ·     Any company or organization that is paying all or part of your rental charges;
      ·     Any intermediary you use, such as a travel agent or broker, in relation to any aspect of your rental;
            and
      ·     Any operator of a membership program for which you are rewarded for renting with us, such as a
            frequent flyer program.
You may quote a special discount code, whether it is referred to as a “CDP number” or a “Promotion
Code” or “PC”,(a “Discount Code”) when you enter into a transaction with us, entitling you to the special
rate or benefits we may have negotiated with ther company, association, credit card company or travel
club sponsoring the Discount Code (the “Discount Code Sponsor”), if you are eligible to do so.
More about Discount Code Sponsors…
If you rent/purchase using a Discount Code, you consent to our disclosure of your personal data to the Discount Code Sponsor to:
• Administer and evaluate the program;
• Confirm your eligibility to use that Discount Code;
• Determine our compliance with the terms of the program;
• Establish your compliance with the sponsor’s policies;
• Enable the sponsor’s payment of your costs (if applicable); or
• For any other uses reserved by a Discount Code Sponsor with you, which may include marketing uses.

If you do not wish us to disclose your personal data to a Discount Code Sponsor for the above purposes, you must not use their Discount
Code for your rental or purchase. This will mean, however, that you will not be able to receive the benefits associated with that Discount
Code.
Protective and legal uses
We may use, share and disclose your personal data for legal reasons as we believe necessary or
appropriate, including:
      ·     under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence;
      ·     to process, handle or otherwise respond to claims for damages, including claims or demands for
            bodily injury or property damage;
      ·     to comply with legal process;
      ·     to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government
            authorities outside your country of residence;
      ·     to enforce our terms and conditions;
      ·     to recover our vehicles or any monies due, such as through debt collection agencies;
      ·     to protect our operations or those of any of our subsidiaries;
      ·     to assess your credit worthiness
      ·     to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our subsidiaries, you or others; and
      ·     to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
Disclosure to our service providers and agents
We may use other companies as our service providers or agents to act on our behalf and assist us in the
conduct of our business, performing services for us under our instruction. These services may include
hosting certain websites or databases, operating “apps” for us on our social media networks’ pages,
running contests, sweepstakes and other promotions for us, sending marketing communications, carrying
out data analysis and conducting customer satisfaction surveys or other research. These services may
also include processing your loan application, title, registration, warranty documents, or vehicle protection
plan documents. We will seek to require our service providers and agents to maintain appropriate
security standards to protect your personal data and use the personal data we provide to them only for
the purposes we specify.
Disclosure for corporate transactions
We may disclose your personal data to a third party in connection with any contemplated or actual
reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of
our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
Marketing Uses and Disclosures
--------------------------------------------------------
We may aggregate your personal data and use it to develop marketing programs and service offerings
that we believe may be of interest to you. We would like to send these to you by email, by text
message or by mail. We would also like to share your personal data with our licensees, affiliates and
business partners for their marketing purposes. You have choices in relation to our marketing uses of
your personal data, based upon the residence for you in our records, as follows:
US residents

We may use your personal data for the above marketing purposes, although you can choose to limit or
restrict our mailings and our sharing of your data for these uses by following the instructions at Marketing
Options below.
EU and Canadian residents
We will only use your personal data for our marketing purposes with your prior consent, which may be
collected from a number of sources.
If you do not receive marketing messages from us and would like to do so, or if you want to limit or restrict
our communications with you or sharing of your data for marketing purposes, please follow the
instructions at Marketing Options below.
Residents of other countries
We aim to comply with your local law regarding our use of your personal data for marketing
purposes. You can instruct us how we can use and disclose your personal data for marketing purposes
by following the instructions at Marketing Options below.
Marketing Options
--------------------------------------------------------
Members of Our membership programs
If you are a member of one of our membership programs, you will have made marketing choices in
connection with the respective program when you enrolled or at such other time(s) as you may have
chosen to do so. These choices are now recorded in your Profile. You can review and amend your
selections for the respective program by accessing your Profile at the Hertz Gold Plus Rewards section
on www.hertz.com or the comparable link for the respective program.
Alternatively, please complete the My Privacy Choices form at the end of this policy and mail it to us,
following the instructions at Contact Us below.
Non-members
We may record your privacy election regarding the receipt of marketing communications at the time you
make a reservation or at other times when you interact with us. If you are not then a member of one of
our membership programs, or the email address provided for the specific reservation/interaction is not
associated with the profile you have in a membership program, you can follow the “Alternate opportunities
to opt-out” instructions below to tell us that you no longer wish to receive marketing communications at
that email address if you previously had elected to receive marketing communications.
In addition, if you are not a member of one of our membership programs, you can record your marketing
choices by enrolling, free of charge, in Hertz Gold Plus Rewards. Please either ask at the rental counter
or visit our Hertz Gold Plus Rewards section on www.hertz.com.
When you enroll, we will provide you with a Hertz Gold Plus Rewards member number and ask you to
quote it when you rent a vehicle from Hertz. We will automatically apply your marketing choices to all
Hertz rentals you make quoting this number. Your choices will be recorded in your Hertz Gold Plus
Rewards Profile and you will be able to amend your choices at any time by following the instructions for
Members of Hertz membership programs above.
Alternative opportunities to opt-out

Our marketing emails contain an unsubscribe option. If you do not want us to continue to send marketing
emails to your email address, click on ‘unsubscribe’ and we will not send further marketing emails to that
address, although you may still receive emails at other addresses for which you have not unsubscribed. If
you subsequently wish to override your choice to unsubscribe, you will need to either amend your Profile
(see Members of Hertz membership programs) or, if you are not a member of one of our programs, follow
the instructions for Non-members above, or at Contact Us below.
Important points to note
Please note the following points about the marketing choices you make:
     ·   If you change your marketing choices, we will observe your most recent choice with regard to the
         contact information associated with your membership number for the relevant membership
         program. To the extent allowed by law, marketing choices you make with regard to one
         membership program will not modify your marketing choices for another membership
         program. Although we aim to process your choices promptly, you may still receive marketing
         communications prepared before we received your request to unsubscribe;
     ·   If you change your address, we will continue to follow your directions for your most recent
         address provided from your ‘unsubscribe’ click noted above, your Profile, or the My Privacy
         Choices form you completed that is associated with you for the implicated membership program.
         In order for us to continue to follow your directions at a new address, you will need to update your
         Profile online or complete another My Privacy Choices form with your updated information and
         provide it to us with your changed contact information; and
     ·   If you choose not to receive marketing messages from us, you may not be able to receive certain
         benefits connected to any program to which you belong, such as promotions involving Hertz Gold
         Plus Rewards points and free rental days (if applicable). You will, however, to the extent
         permitted by law continue to receive applicable program updates and other membership
         information; and
     ·   If your Profile contains a customer discount program (CDP) number, your CDP sponsor may have
         made marketing choices for users of that CDP, PC or affiliation. If the sponsor’s choices are
         more restrictive on our use of your data than your choices, we will observe the choices made by
         the sponsor in connection with those transactions in which such CDP, PC or affiliation is used.
Contact Us
We hope this policy answers your questions about our collection, use and disclosure of your personal
data. If you have additional questions or want to contact us for a specific purpose, please select from the
following:
Access/Corrections: Please send any request to access, amend or delete certain personal data we hold
about you to the most convenient contact address below.
Complaints and other questions: You should send any questions you may have about this policy or any
complaints you have about how we have handled our personal data to the most convenient contact
address below. If you feel our response is not satisfactory, we will refer you to a neutral and independent
dispute resolution organization.

Marketing: Send a completed My Privacy Choices form (at the end of the policy) to the most convenient
contact address below. We aim to process your choices promptly on receipt, but you should please allow
a number of days for your choices to become effective.
Security: If you have reason to believe that the personal data we hold about you, such as your account
with Hertz Car Sales, Hertz Gold Plus Rewards member number, other program Profile(s), or other
membership information is no longer secure, you must immediately notify us of the problem by either
clicking “Contact Us” on any page of www.hertzcarsales.com, www.hertz.com, or www.hertzequip.com;
or calling as follows:
     ·   Customers in the United States: (800) 654-4173 or (888) 674-3309
     ·   Customers outside the United States: 001 (405) 775-3400
US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Enforcement: Please raise any concerns regarding our
compliance with the US-EU Safe Harbor Principles and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles by clicking
“Contact Us” on any page of www.hertzcarsales.com, www.hertz.com, or www.hertzequip.com; or
writing to us at any of the addresses below. We have committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints
under the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Principals and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent
dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business
Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not
satisfactorily addressed by us, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-
harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.
Contact addresses:
• Director, Privacy Services, The Hertz Corporation, P.O. Box 25301, Oklahoma City, OK 73125, U.S.A.
• Director, Privacy Services, Hertz Europe Service Centre, Swords Business Park, Swords, Co. Dublin,
Republic of Ireland
• Privacy Compliance Officer, Hertz Australia Pty Limited, Level 6, 10 Dorcas Street, South Melbourne
VIC 3205, Australia
• Director, Privacy Services, Hertz New Zealand Ltd., Private Bag 4716, Christchurch, New Zealand 8020

My Privacy Choices
--------------------------------------------------------
Please complete this form and send it to us by following the instructions at Contact Us above.
(Updates: Please update your information in your Profile online, or use this form for changes.)
Please note: Privacy Choices for our Dollar Rent A Car, Thrifty Rent A Car, or FireFly Rent-A-Car businesses or Donlen Corporation should
be made by following instructions in their respective privacy policies.
Name: ..................................................................
Address: ....................................................     State/Province: .....................................................
Zip/Post
                                                                  Country: ......................................................
code: ...................................................
Email                                                             Hertz Gold Plus Rewards Member
Address: ...................................................      Number: .....................................................
A. Please send me marketing offers and materials from or on behalf of Hertz:
                                                           Yes            No
 Postal mail                                                  [ ]         [ ]
 E-mail                                                       [ ]         [ ]
B. Please share my personal data with Hertz’s licensees, affiliates and business partners for their
marketing purposes:
                                                           Yes            No
                                                            [ ]          [ ]
Any consent regarding your receiving marketing materials provided above can be withdrawn or
other otherwise changed at any time in accordance with the instructions set forth in this Privacy
Policy.
